class QuestionModel{
  final String question;
  final List<String> option;
  final int correctAnswerIndex;


  const QuestionModel({
    required this.correctAnswerIndex,
    required this.question,
    required this.option,

  });
}

const List<QuestionModel> questions =[
  QuestionModel(
     question:'1.MIME stands for ', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 0,
     option: [
      'a) Multimedia Internet Mail Extensions',
      'b) Multipurpose Internet Multimedia Extensions',
      'c) Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions',
      'd) Multiple Internet Mail Extensions',
     ]
     ),
     

     QuestionModel(
     question:'2. …………… attribute of a table determine how much space there is between the contents of a cell and its border.', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 2,
     option: [
      'a) cellspacing',
      'b) margin',
      'c) cellpadding',
      'd) cellborder',
     ]
     ),
     

     QuestionModel(
     question:'3. ………………tag is used to include javascript into the HTML page.', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 1,
     option: [
      'a) <link>',
      'b) <script>',
      'c) <javascript>',
      'd) <style>',
     ],
     ),


       QuestionModel(
     question:'4. In javascript what does is NaN function do?', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 0,
     option: [
      'a) Return true if the argument is not a number ',
      'b) Return false if the argument is not a number',
      'c) Return true if the argument is a number ',
      'd) None of the above ',
     ],
     ),
     

            QuestionModel(
     question:'5. …………method is used to remove focus from the specified object.', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 0,
     option: [
      'a) blur()',
      'b) unload()',
      'c) focus()',
      'd) removefocus()',
     ],
     ),


            QuestionModel(
     question:'6. Javascript code can be called by using', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 3,
     option: [
      'a) method',
      'b) preprocessor',
      'c) RMI',
      'd) triggering event',
     ],
     ),



            QuestionModel(
     question:'7. In PHP ……………. tests a variable to see whether it has been assigned a value.', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 1,
     option: [
      'a) set()',
      'b) isNull()',
      'c) isSet()',
      'd) None',
     ],
     ),


            QuestionModel(
     question:'8. Which is not an attribute of the cookie property', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 1,
     option: [
      'a) path',
      'b) host',
      'c) secure',
      'd) domain',
     ],
     ),

            QuestionModel(
     question:'9.To use mysql on your computer, youll need', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 3,
     option: [
      'a) Perl, PHP or Java',
      'b) FTP and Telnet',
      'c) Browser',
      'd) All of them',
     ],
     ),


            QuestionModel(
     question:'10. To remove duplicate rows from the result set of a SELECT use the following keyword:', 
     correctAnswerIndex: 2,
     option: [
      'a) NO DUPLICATE',
      'b) UNIQUE',
      'c) DISTINCT',
      'd) None of the above',
     ],
     ),
];

